http://www.bvwhc.org/contents/about/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy - Boulder, CO & Longmont, CO: Boulder Valley Women's Health Center
Privacy Policy
Boulder Valley Women’s Health Center (Women’s Health) wants this site to be a safe and private place for users. We respect and protect the privacy of those who visit or use our website.There are certain actions and areas of the site that will require you to provide personal information, such as:Signing-up to receive the Women’s Health newsletter by emailMaking a donationResponding to a surveyFilling out a formAny time you provide personal information, this privacy policy will govern our use of the information you have providedWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, make a donation, respond to a survey, or fill out a form. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.When making a donation, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and/or credit card information.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:• To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you;• To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the service or making the donation requested;• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature;• To send periodic emails.  The email address you provide for making a donation may be used to send you information and updates about Women’s Health.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you make an online donation.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes, we use cookies.  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to help us remember and process your donation transaction and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our features may not function properly. However, you can still make a donation over the telephone by calling 303-440-9320, ext. 11.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe value your privacy, and therefore we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act, which is considered the gold standard for online privacy protection. We will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  We reserve the right to modify our privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently.This policy was last modified on 3/2/2010.Contacting UsIf you wish to correct your contact information, provide a change of address, or if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us using the information below.Women’s Health2855 Valmont RoadBoulder, Colorado 80301U.S.Ainfo@bvwhc.orghttp://www.boulderwomenshealth.org
Donate Now                                   Join Mailing list
Address: 2855 Valmont Rd,
Address: 82 21st Ave, Suite C,
Longmont, CO 80501
×
